<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</title>
    <link>/tags/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 20:45:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install (Oracle) Sun Java SDK 1.6.x (Java 6) on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>/2011/01/how-to-install-oracle-sun-java-sdk-1-6-x-java-6-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2011 20:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2011/01/how-to-install-oracle-sun-java-sdk-1-6-x-java-6-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Beitrag beschreibt die Installation des Sun Java SDK 1.6.x on Ubuntu (Maverick). The English explanation on how to install Sun Java SDK 1.6.x can be found here.
Canonical-Partner Repositories aktivieren: Dies geschieht unter “System” -&amp;gt; “Systemverwaltung” -&amp;gt; “Synaptic Paketverwalung”. In der Paketverwaltung finden sich die Paketquellen unter dem Menüpunkt “Einstellungen”. In den Einstellungen wechselt man auf den Reiter “Andere Software” und aktiviert dort “Canonical-Partner” bzw. “Canonical-Partner (Quelltext)”. Nach dem Klick auf “Schließen” werden die Paketlisten neu geladen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Broadcom Wireless Device on HP Mini 5101 running Ubuntu Jaunty</title>
      <link>/2009/09/howto-install-broadcom-wireless-device-on-hp-mini-5101-running-ubuntu-jaunty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 17:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/09/howto-install-broadcom-wireless-device-on-hp-mini-5101-running-ubuntu-jaunty/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I received my new HPMini 5101 running Suse Linux Enterprise Desktop11 (SLED 11). Due to the fact, that i do not like working with Suse I installed Ubuntu 9.04but there were some problems regarding the wireless chipset (Broadcom5343) and the Ethernetadapter (Marvel 436c).
After installation the wireless and the ethernet devices were not working. The problem was that I needed to install proprietary drivers which were not included in Ubuntu due to licence issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>