<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Searching on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</title>
    <link>/tags/searching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Searching on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 18:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/searching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[video] – How fast is Google Chrome?</title>
      <link>/2010/05/video-how-fast-is-google-chrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 18:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/05/video-how-fast-is-google-chrome/</guid>
      <description>These days Googlehas released a videodemonstrating the speed of their new betaGoogle Chromebrowser. The video is made up in a very creative way. I am impressed how Google always finds really interesting ways to promote their products. Specially this one is of really interest:
For everybody who is interested in the making of this video will like the following one too:
(via ReadWriteWeband Mashable)
Related articles     Google Chrome: The New Beta is Faster Than Ever (techie-buzz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Wave – Google’s next killer application?</title>
      <link>/2009/05/google-wave-googles-next-killer-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2009 09:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/05/google-wave-googles-next-killer-application/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;dd class=&amp;quot;wp-caption-dd zemanta-img-attribution&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Image by &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/87956460@N00/3575380674&amp;quot;&amp;gt;liako&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; via Flickr &amp;lt;/dd&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dl&amp;gt;  Google’snewest prodcut which was announced at the GoogleI/Othis week is called Google Wave. They build an incredible tool for collaborative work and integrated services like email, instant messenging, collaborative editing, an incredible spell checkerwhich checks the context of words in order to correct spelling. Other really greate features are gadgetslike:
 linky: adds links automatically while you type searchy: lets you search the internet through the application and integrate the searched contend into a wave buggy: through buggy you are able to interact with bug trackingsoftwareand easily administer bugs  This are just some kind of great tools available in Google Wave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[video] – Google Latitude</title>
      <link>/2009/02/video-google-latitude/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 09:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/02/video-google-latitude/</guid>
      <description>Googlereleased a new service called Google Latitude. This service enables you to see the location of your friends, collegues, etc. Here is a nice video explaining how Google Latitute workes:
[youtube Q-Oq-9enE-k]
Related articles by Zemanta    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple iPhone</title>
      <link>/2007/04/apple-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2007 13:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2007/04/apple-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Hier ein sehr interessantes Video über das neue iPhone von Apple! Viel Spaß damit! Google Maps on iPhone:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YRNugqEQYS4</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
