<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New York Times on Herbert Mühlburger</title>
    <link>/tags/new-york-times/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New York Times on Herbert Mühlburger</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 17:36:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/new-york-times/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[video] – The Filter Bubble – From Human to Algorithmic Gatekeepers</title>
      <link>/2011/05/video-the-filter-bubble-from-human-to-algorithmic-gatekeepers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2011 17:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2011/05/video-the-filter-bubble-from-human-to-algorithmic-gatekeepers/</guid>
      <description>Web personalization and personalized recommendations are recently gaining more and more interest. Companies like Amazon, Google, Netflix, The New York Times, Facebook, Twitter, … already personalize their products in different ways. If you take Google’s search results as an example. Have you ever noticed that a friend of you gets different search results as you do for the same search query? If you never have noticed just try it out it’s really worth noting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Flu Trends – Google Uses Searches to Track Flu’s Spread</title>
      <link>/2008/11/google-flu-trends-google-uses-searches-to-track-flu-spread/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2008 09:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/2008/11/google-flu-trends-google-uses-searches-to-track-flu-spread/</guid>
      <description>It stands to reason that people who are “starting to come down with something” often take the opportunity to search for information on what ails them, even before they discuss their symptoms with a healthcare professional. Who gets more of those searches than anyone? Google, of course. [ReadWriteWeb]&#xA;Google offers a new service called Google Flu Trends. The service uses an analysis of Google’s millions of search queries every day to calculate flu trends.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
