<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Languages on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</title>
    <link>/tags/languages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Languages on IT-ZT DI Herbert Mühlburger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 12:55:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/languages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Robotium – A Testing Framework for Android</title>
      <link>/2011/04/introducing-robotium-a-testing-framework-for-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2011 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2011/04/introducing-robotium-a-testing-framework-for-android/</guid>
      <description>Robotiumis an open sourcetesting framework for Androidapplications. It makes it easy to write complex black-box testcases. Test driven developmentis a methology where tests are written before the actual application.
  Write a testcase  Watch it failing
  Write the actual source codein you application which enables the test to pass
  Watch the test passing
  Go back to step 1
  The following video gives you an introduction into Robotium:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaFX Links of the Week 1, February 2010</title>
      <link>/2010/02/javafx-links-of-the-week-1-february-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2010 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/02/javafx-links-of-the-week-1-february-2010/</guid>
      <description>Today I decided to post regularly interesting JavaFX links of the past week. Thanks to Jonathan Gilesfor his great posts on “Java Desktop Links of the Week”. The JavaFX links are just taken from Jonathan’s posts in order to build a little JavaFX news archieve on my own blog and to inform my subscribers on interesting JavaFX news.
Here are the JavaFX Links of the Week 1, February 2010:
  Jim Weaver sums up the Oracle news this week nice and succinctly: ‘We will invest heavily in JavaFX‘.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Tutorial] – Java Online Programming Course</title>
      <link>/2009/10/tutorial-java-online-programming-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2009 19:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/10/tutorial-java-online-programming-course/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;dd class=&amp;quot;wp-caption-dd zemanta-img-attribution&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dd&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/dl&amp;gt;  For everybody who likes to learn the Java programming languageor who is forced to learn Java I have found a great online tutorialteaching you the essence of Java programming. Specially students should pay attention to this course as it gives a really good introduction to the Java programming language.
The online course can be found here.
Enjoy learning Java and afterwards take a look at JavaFX.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
